Guide to the Donald Oliver/Chelsea Music Archive, 1907-2008 (bulk 1962-1991) MSS.254
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Conductor Scores and Orchestrations
  This series consists of piano conductor scores, master scores and parts, and full orchestrations for Broadway and off-Broadway productions. The bulk of the collection consists of bound and handwritten "green-books" and spiral-bound piano conductor scores. This series also comprises production scores for several theater personalities, including cabaret singer Marti Stevens (b.1933) and librettist and lyricist Dorothy Fields (1905-1974). Also included in this series are full orchestrations for Mandy Patinkin's stage productions of his albums Kidults and Mama-Loshn.
  - Alice, 1978 (Box 21, Item 1)
  - Alice in Wonderland, undated (Box 21, Item 2)
  - Annie, 1978 (Box 21, Item 3)
  - The Baker's Wife [1 of 2], 1976 (Box 22, Item 1)
  - The Baker's Wife [2 of 2], 1976 (Box 22, Item 2)
  - Big Deal, 1986 (Box 22, Item 3)
  - Breakfast at Tiffany's [1 of 3], 1966 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - Breakfast at Tiffany's [2 of 3], 1966 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Breakfast at Tiffany's [3 of 3], 1966 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - Carmelina, 1979 (Box 24, Item 1)
  - Curtains, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - Fields, Dorothy [Miscellaneous Scores 1 of 2], 1934-1970 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Fields, Dorothy [Miscellaneous Scores 2 of 2], 1934-1970 (Box 25, Item 1)
  - Floyd Collins, 1998 (Box 25, Item 2)
  - George M. [Act 1 and Act 2], 1969 (Box 25, Item 3)
  - Give Him the Oo-la-la [from Cole Porter's DuBarry Was a Lady], undated (Box 26, Item 1)
  - Going Hollywood, undated (Box 26, Item 2)
  - Guys and Dolls [1 of 2], 1992 (Box 26, Item 3)
  - Guys and Dolls [2 of 2], 1992 (Box 27, Item 1)
  - The Happy Time, 1983 (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Harry Blackstone Magic Show, 1980 (Box 27, Item 3)
  - Hazel Kirke, 1987 (Box 28, Item 1)
  - Home Again, 1979 (Box 28, Item 2)
  - I Love My Wife, 1979 (Box 28, Item 3)
  - Into the Woods, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Item 1)
  - Irene, 1973 (Box 29, Item 2)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar, [1971?] (Box 29, Item 3, Box 73)
  - Kicks & Co., 1961 (Box 30, Item 1)
  - King: A Musical based on the Life of Martin Luther King, Jr., 1983-1987 (Box 30, Item 2)
  - King of Hearts [1 of 2], 1978 (Box 30, Item 3)
  - King of Hearts [2 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Item 1)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman, 1990 (Box 31, Item 2)
  - Little Women, 1958 (Box 31, Item 3)
  - Mademoiselle Colombe, [1987] (Box 32, Item 1)
  - Marilyn, 1983 (Box 32, Item 2)
  - Me and My Girl, [1986] (Box 32, Item 3)
  - The Me Nobody Knows, 1970 (Box 33, Item 1)
  - Merrily We Roll Along, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Item 2)
  - Noel, 1981 (Box 33, Item 3)
  - On the Town, 1977 (Box 34, Item 1)
  - Once Upon a Song, 1991 (Box 34, Item 2)
  - One Night Stand, 1980 (Box 34, Item 3)
  - Over Here!, 1974 (Box 39, Item 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults [1 of 6], [2000] (Box 35, Item 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults [2 of 6], [2000] (Box 35, Item 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults [3 of 6], [2000] (Box 35, Item 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults [4 of 6], [2000] (Box 36, Item 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults [5 of 6], [2000] (Box 36, Item 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults [6 of 6], [2000] (Box 36, Item 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn [1 of 6], 1997-1998 (Box 37, Item 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn [2 of 6], 1997-1998 (Box 37, Item 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn [3 of 6], 1997-1998 (Box 37, Item 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn [4 of 6], 1997-1998 (Box 38, Item 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn [5 of 6], 1997-1998 (Box 38, Item 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn [6 of 6], 1997-1998 (Box 38, Item 3)
  - Peg, 1983 (Box 39, Item 2)
  - Phantom of the Opera, [1988] (Box 39, Item 3)
  - Platinum, 1970 (Box 40, Item 1)
  - Rock-a-bye Hamlet, 1976 (Box 40, Item 2)
  - Romance...Romance, 1988 (Box 40, Item 3)
  - Shlomo [1 of 3], [2008] (Box 41, Item 1)
  - Shlomo [2 of 3], [2008] (Box 41, Item 2)
  - Shlomo [3 of 3], [2008] (Box 41, Item 3)
  - She Loves Me, undated (Box 42, Item 1)
  - Somethings Afoot, 1976 (Box 42, Item 2)
  - Song of Norway, [1972] (Box 42, Item 3)
  - Sophisticated Ladies Moscow Tour [1 of 2], 1981 (Box 43, Item 1)
  - Sophisticated Ladies Moscow Tour [2 of 2], 1981 (Box 43, Item 2)
  - Stevens, Marti [Miscellaneous Scores], [1999] (Box 43, Item 3)
  - Swing, 1980 (Box 44, Item 1)
  - Timbuktu, 1978 (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona, [1971] (Box 44, Item 3)
  - Ulysses, 1974 (Box 45, Item 1)
  - West Side Story/Katie Couric Cancer Benefit [1 of 5], 2002 (Box 45, Item 2)
  - West Side Story/Katie Couric Cancer Benefit [2 of 5], 2002 (Box 45, Item 3)
  - West Side Story/Katie Couric Cancer Benefit [3 of 5], 2002 (Box 46, Item 1)
  - West Side Story/Katie Couric Cancer Benefit [4 of 5], 2002 (Box 46, Item 2)
  - West Side Story/Katie Couric Cancer Benefit [5 of 5], 2002 (Box 46, Item 3)
  - The Wizard of Oz [1 of 2], 1987 (Box 47, Item 1)
  - The Wizard of Oz [2 of 2], 1987 (Box 47, Item 2)
  - The Young Mark Twain, undated (Box 47, Item 3)
- Series IV: Video Recordings
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
  - A Chorus Line, circa 1975; ID: 254.0001 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0001, Box Shared Fales 139, Dvd 254.0001)
    Access DVD available by appointment.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Original Format: VHS
    Duration: 02:04:00
  - American Dance Machine, undated; ID: 254.0009 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0009, Box Shared Fales 139, Dvd 254.0009)
    Duration: 01:00:00
  - Anastasia Game, 1989; ID: 254.0012 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0012, Box Shared Fales 139, Dvd 254.0012)
    Duration: 02:01:00
    8:45 PM, October 14, 1989
  - Andre Heller's Wonderhouse, 1991; ID: 254.0010 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0010, Box Shared Fales 139, Dvd 254.0010)
    Duration: 01:45:00
    Broadhurst Theatre (Orchestra E-2) 2nd Preview: Saturday Matinee, October 12, 1991
  - Andre Heller's Wonderhouse, undated; ID: 254.0011 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0011, Box Shared Fales 139, Dvd 254.0011)
    Duration: 1:33:00
  - Annie 2 Miss Hannigan's Revenge, 1990; ID: 254.0013 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0013, Box Shared Fales 139, Dvd 254.0013_pt.1, Dvd 254.0013_pt.2)
    Access DVD available by appointment. Please request Part 1 and/or Part 2.
    Duration: 02:16:37 Part 1 01:21:10 Part 2
    Closing: January 20, 1990
  - Aspects of Love, 1990; ID: 254.0014 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0014, Box Shared Fales 139, Dvd 254.0014)
    Duration: 02:22:48
  - Assasins "Conversation Piece", 1991; ID: 254.0015 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0015, Box 74, Dvd 254.0015)
    Duration: 01:07:02
  - Bent, undated; ID: 254.0016 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0016, Box 74, Dvd 254.0016)
    Duration: 01:43:50
  - Black & Blue, 1989; ID: 254.0017 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0017, Box 74, Dvd 254.0017)
    Duration: 02:03:43
    Original Broadway Cast, 5/17/1989
  - Broadway Highlights, undated; ID: 254.0019 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0019)
    Currently there is no access to this title. Please contact Fales Library.
    Duration: Unknown
    Misc. newsreels and promotional footage
  - Cabaret- Donmar Warehouse, undated; ID: 254.0020 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0020, Box 74, Dvd 254.0020)
    Duration: 01:52:29
  - Can-Can, 1988; ID: 254.0022 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0022, Box 74, Dvd 254.0022)
    Duration: 02:02:00
    Chita Rivera and Ron Holgate, Hartford, CT, 6/9/88
  - Candide, 1982; ID: 254.0023 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0023)
    NY City Opera
  - Case of the Dead Flamigo Dancer, 1990; ID: 254.0008 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0008, Box 74, Dvd 254.0008)
    Duration: 01:35:00
    Promenade Theater (F-1) Monday, August 6, 1990
  - Chicago, undated; ID: 254.0025 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0025, Box 74, Dvd 254.0025)
  - Dance a Little Closer, undated; ID: 254.0027 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0027, Box 74, Dvd 254.0027)
    Duration: 02:05:00
  - Dances of Carousel, 1993; ID: 254.0028 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0028, Box 74, Dvd 254.0028)
    Duration: 01:13:45
  - Dangerous Games, 1989; ID: 254.0029 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0029, Box 74, Dvd 254.0029)
    Duration: 01:49:38
    Nederlander Theatre October 12, 1989
  - Dreamgirls, undated; ID: 254.0030 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0030, Box 74, Dvd 254.0030)
    Duration: 02:12:00
  - Elegant Films, Inc. "The Amazing Journey 25 Years of Tommy", 1993; ID: 254.0031 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0031, Box 74, Dvd 254.0031)
    July 30, 1993
  - An Evening w/Alan Jay Lerner- England, undated; ID: 254.0033 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0033, Box 74, Dvd 254.0033)
  - Evita, undated; ID: 254.0037 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0037)
  - Follies, 1988; ID: 254.0005 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0005, Box 74, Dvd 254.0005)
    Duration: 02:29:45
    Fisher Theatre, Detroit. Opening Night: October 21, 1988.
  - Follies, undated; ID: 254.0038 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0038, Box 74, Dvd 254.0038)
    Duration: 00:39:30
    Original Broadway Production
  - 42nd Street, undated; ID: 254.0039 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0039, Box 74, Dvd 254.0039)
    Duration: 01:54:00
  - [1]--42nd Street [2]--We're In The Money, undated; ID: 254.0040 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0040, Box 74, Dvd 254.0040)
    Duration: 00:47:00
  - The Golden Apple, 1995; ID: 254.0042 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0042, Box 74, Dvd 254.0042)
    Duration: 02:16:58
    John LaTouche & Jerome Moross. Light Opera Works, Evanstone, IL. August 27, 1995.
  - Grand Hotel, circa 1989; ID: 254.0043 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0043, Box 74, Dvd 254.0043)
    Original Broadway Cast. Filmed at the Martin Beck Theater in New York City.
    Duration: 02:03:44
    Audio is out of sync with image. Image quality is fair.
  - Grand Hotel (workshop), April 21, 1989; ID: 254.0044 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0044, Box 74, Dvd 254.0044)
    Duration: 01:09:39
    Image quality is poor.
    Early workshop for original Broadway production.
  - Gypsy, undated; ID: 254.0045 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0045, Box 74, Dvd 254.0045_pt.1, Dvd 254.0045_pt.2)
    Duration: 01:23:00 Part 1 01:21:00 Part 2
  - A Handful of Keys, 1995; ID: 254.0046 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0046, Box 74, Dvd 254.0046)
    Duration: 02:40:00
    A musical tribute to Martin Smith. Prince Edward Theatre. November 5, 1995.
  - Martin Smith's A Handful of Keys, undated; ID: 254.0060 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0060, Box 74, Dvd 254.0060)
    Duration: 01:30:00
  - Into the Woods, 1990; ID: 254.0050 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0050, Box 74, Dvd 254.0050)
    A Conversation Piece with Stephen Sondheim and James Lapine. An author's video guids to producing Into the Woods. (c) Music Theatre International, 1990.
  - Keystone, undated; ID: 254.0052 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0052, Box 74, Dvd 254.0052)
    Duration: 02:15:00
    with Ann Morrison & Wayne Bryan
  - King, 1988; ID: 254.0053 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0053, Box 74, Dvd 254.0053)
    Duration: 00:47:55
    London, Live. April 10, 1988.
  - Legs Diamond, 1989; ID: 254.0055 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0055, Box 74, Dvd 254.0055)
    Duration: 02:00:00
    with Peter Allen & Julie Wilson. Mark Hellinger Theatre, January 14, 1989.
  - Terrence McNally's The Lisbon Traviata, 1989; ID: 254.0087 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0087, Box 74, Dvd 254.0087)
    Performed Sunday evening, 26 November 1989 at the Promenade Theatre
    Starring Anthony Heald, Nathan Lane, Dan Butler, and John Slattery
  - A Little Night Music, 1990; ID: 254.0056 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0056, Box 74, Dvd 254.0056_pt.1, Dvd 254.0056_pt.2)
    Duration: 01:43:00 Part 1 01:08:00 Part 2
    Live from NYC Opera, November 7, 1990.
  - Mame, undated; ID: 254.0059 (Box 70, Media ID: 254.0059, Box 74, Dvd 254.0059)
    Duration: 02:19:30
  - Master Class, undated; ID: 254.0002 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0002, Box 74, Dvd 254.0002)
    Featuring Zoe Caldwell
    Duration: 02:30:00
  - Merrily We Roll Along, undated; ID: 254.0061 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0061, Box 74, Dvd 254.0061)
    Duration: 01:54:38
  - Metropolis (London), undated; ID: 254.0062 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0062, Box 74, Dvd 254.0062)
  - [1]--Murder at the Vanities [2]--The Cookie Lady, 1982; ID: 254.0065 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0065, Box 74, Dvd 254.0065)
    May 5, 1982, 8:30PM
  - Nymph Errant, 1989; ID: 254.0069 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0069, Box 74, Dvd 254.0069)
    London, May 21, 1989.
  - On Your Toes, December 14, 1983; ID: 254.0070 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0070, Box 74, Dvd 254.0070)
    Duration: 120 minutes
    Image quality is lesser than DVD #254.0071 and 254.0072
  - On Your Toes (Act 1), December 14, 1983; ID: 254.0072 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0072)
    Broadway production. Filmed at the Virginia Theatre.
    Duration: 63 minutes
  - On Your Toes (Act 2), December 14, 1983; ID: 254.0071 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0071)
  - Pacific Overtures (Part 1), 1976; ID: 254.0073 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0073, Box 74, Dvd 254.0073)
    Live
  - [1]--Pacific Overtures (Part 2)[2]--Pirates of Penzances, undated; ID: 254.0074 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0074, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0074)
  - Quilt (copy MCC), undated; ID: 254.0078 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0078, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0078)
  - Re-Opening of the Shubert Theater, New Haven, CT., undated; ID: 254.0067 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0067, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0067)
  - Sherlock Holmes, undated; ID: 254.0007 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0007, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0007)
    Duration: 02:20:30
    London.
  - Slay It with Music: A Musical Chiller, 1989; ID: 254.0082 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0082, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0082)
    Performed 8pm Sunday, 22 October 1989 at Actors Outlet Theatre, 120 West 28th Street
    With Virginia Sandifur Directed by Charles Repole Choreography by Dennis Dennehy Music and Lyrics by Michael Colby Book by Paul Katz Presented by Broadway Tomorrow and Michael Colby
  - Steel Pier, undated; ID: 254.0004 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0004, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0004)
    Duration: 02:24:00
    Broadway
  - Surprise, undated; ID: 254.0006 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0006, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0006)
    Duration: 00:42:30
    East Hampton
  - Sweeney Todd, undated; ID: 254.0086 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0086, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0086)
  - Tintypes, 1981; ID: 254.0088 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0088, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0088)
    Closing performance on Broadway: 11 Jan 1981
  - Tommy, undated; ID: 254.0089 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0089, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0089)
  - Tommy, 1993; ID: 254.0090 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0090, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0090)
    Broadway special. 19 April 1993.
  - Victor/Victoria, 1997; ID: 254.0103 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0103, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0103)
    With Liza Minnelli.
  - Whorehouse, undated; ID: 254.0105 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0105, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0105)
    Closing performance.
  - [1]--Zombies from the Beyond [2]--Ethel Merman on Broadway, 1995; 1959; ID: 254.0107 (Box 71, Media ID: 254.0107, Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 254.0107)
    [1] directed by James Valo, staged by Pam Kriger at the Players Theatre. Wednesday evening, 18 October 1995.
    [2] 24 November 1959
  - Video Preservation Discontinued - CLOSED (Box Shared Fales PM 71)
    Scope and Contents
    Contains preservation masters and sub-masters for Source IDs 254.0002 - 254.0007
    CLOSED
- Series V: Paper Documentation from Video Recordings
  This series consists of newspaper clippings originally housed with the video recordings in Series IV. They have been photocopied for preservation purposes. Each item includes the media ID of the video recording to which the item corresponds.
  - The Anastasia Game [254.0012], undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Dangerous Games [254.0029], [1989] (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Oversize Series I: Librettos and Playbills
  - Maggie May Libretto, [1964] (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Oversize Series III: Conductor Scores and Orchestrations
  - The Amourous Flea Piano Conductor Score, [1964] (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Anyone Can Whistle Act I Piano Conductor Score, [1964] (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Anyone Can Whistle Act II Piano Conductor Score, [1964] (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Barnum Act I Piano Conductor Score [annotated with Michael Stewart's red notes], 1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Barnum Act II Piano Conductor Score [annotated with Michael Stewart's red notes], 1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Brainchild/"I'm Tired of Me" (1), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Brainchild/"Everything that Happens to You Happens to Me" (1A), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Brainchild/"There Are No Faceless People in My World" (2), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Brainchild/"Bluebird" (3), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Brainchild/"I Know You Are There" (4), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Brainchild/"Many People Live Inside My Mind" (A), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Brainchild/"Don't Talk Don't Think" (5), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Brainchild/"Low Bottom Women" (6), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Brainchild/"I've Been Starting Tomorrow" (7), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Brainchild/"Let Me Think For You" (7A), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Brainchild/"I Never Met a Russian I Didn't Like" (8) [transposed to Bb], 1974 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Brainchild/"Sally Ensalada" (9), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Brainchild/"Let Me Be Your Arrow" (10), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Brainchild/"Beginning Act 2" (10A), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Brainchild/"Just A Little Space Can Be a Growing Place" (11), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Brainchild/"What Is It" (12), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Brainchild/"Sally Crossover" (12A), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Brainchild/"Don't Pull Up the Flowers" (13), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Brainchild/"Everything that Happens to You Happens to Me" (14) [E6 version], 1974 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Candide Full Score [1 of 2], undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Candide Full Score [2 of 2], undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Cyrano/Opening Scene, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Cyrano/"Prelude", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Cyrano/"Bergerac", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Cyrano/"A Man Without Words", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Cyrano/"End of Duel", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Cyrano/"Gascogne" (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Cyrano/"Gascon Flute Song", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Cyrano/"Panache" [1/17 Version], January 17, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Cyrano/"Almond Tarts", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Cyrano/"Almond Tarts" [1/15 Version], January 15, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Cyrano/"A Moment Comes", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Cyrano/"Tell Her", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Cyrano/"The Nose", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Cyrano/"From Now Till Forever", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Cyrano/"[From Now] Till Forever" Utility, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Cyrano/"Amorous Moron", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Cyrano/"I Never Loved You", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Cyrano/"Mime Sequence", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Cyrano/"Mont Fleury Mime" [1 and 2], 1973 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Cyrano/"To Bakery", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Cyrano/"No Thank You", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Cyrano/"No Thank You" [2/24 Version], February 24, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Cyrano/"No Thank You" [3/15 Version], March 15, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Cyrano/"Roxana", 1973 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Cyrano/Act II Finale, February 19, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Damn Yankees Piano Conductor Score, [1955] (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - The Fantasticks Piano Conductor Score, [1960] (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes Piano Conductor Score, [1949] (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Grease Piano Conductor Score, [1972] (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Hazel Kirke/Opening, Prelude and Finale 3 Scores [1 of 3], 1987 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Hazel Kirke/Opening, Prelude and Finale 3 Scores [2 of 3], 1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Hazel Kirke/Opening, Prelude and Finale 3 Scores [3 of 3], 1987 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - I Love My Wife/"Friends", February 1979 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Juno and the Paycock Master Scores [1 of 2], August 13, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Juno and the Paycock Master Scores [2 of 2], August 13, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Little Me Act I Piano Conductor Score, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Little Me Act II Piano Conductor Score, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Magdalena [Revised] Piano Conductor Score, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Marilyn Score, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Merrily We Roll Along Piano Conductor Score, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Ann/"Merman Medley" Scores, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Minnelli, Liza/Miscellaneous Scores ["Paris is a Lonely Town" and "Le Temps"], undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - The Night that Made America Famous Scores, [1975] (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Pacific Overtures Piano Conductor Score, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Pajama Game Act I Piano Conductor Score, [1973] (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Pajama Game Act II Piano Conductor Score, [1973] (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "A Tisket, A Tasket", December 30, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "If I Only Had a Brain", 2000 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "'A' You're Adorable/Getting to Know You" [1 of 2], 2000 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "'A' You're Adorable/Getting to Know You [2 of 2], 2000 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Inch Worm/Schools Days/Time in a Bottle", 2000 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "The Ugly Duckling", 2000 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Not While I'm Around", [1999] (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Everybody Says Don't/King's Clothes" [1 of 2], 1999 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Everybody Says Don't/King's Clothes" [2 of 2], 1999 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "April in Fairbanks", [2000] (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "How Could You Believe Me", December 30, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Japanese Sandman/Cat's in the Cradle", 2000 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Soon It's Gonna Rain"Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Soon It's Gonna Rain", 2000 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Swinging on a Star", 2000 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "The Minute Waltz", 2000 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Holiday for Strings", 2000 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Rhode Island is Famous for You", 2000 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Singing in the Bathtub" [1 of 2], 2000 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Kidults, "Singing in the Bathtub" [2 of 2], 2000 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 1 & 2 [1 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 1 & 2 [2 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 1 & 2 [3 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 1 & 2 [4 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 3 & 4 [1 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 3 & 4 [2 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 3 & 4 [3 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Orchestrator Score Sessions 3 & 4 [4 of 4], 1997 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn Empty Folders, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Hey, Tsigeleh (Hi Little Goats)", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Yome, Yome", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Papirosen", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Rozhinkes Mit Mandln", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Rabbi Elimeylekh", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Take Me Out to the Ball Game/God Bless America", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Ten Kopeks", July 20, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 7)